<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE pkgmetadata SYSTEM "http://www.gentoo.org/dtd/metadata.dtd">
<pkgmetadata>
  <herd>video</herd>
  <maintainer>
    <email>aballier@gentoo.org</email>
    <name>Alexis Ballier</name>
  </maintainer>
  <use>
    <flag name="atmo">Enables support for AtmoLight (homebrew Ambient Lighting Technology)</flag>
    <flag name="cddax">Enables audio CD plugin with CD Text and CD paranoia via libcdio</flag>
    <flag name="cdio">Enables CD input and control library support.</flag>
    <flag name="dc1394">Enables IIDC cameras support.</flag>
    <flag name="dirac">Enable Dirac video support (an advanced royalty-free video compression format) via the reference library: dirac.</flag>
    <flag name="fluidsynth">Enables Fluidsynth MIDI software synthesis (with external sound fonts).</flag>
    <flag name="gcrypt">Enables cryptography support via libgcrypt.</flag>
    <flag name="gnome">Adds support for GNOME's filesystem abstraction layer, <pkg>gnome-base/gnome-vfs</pkg>. This flag is not GUI-related.</flag>
    <flag name="httpd">Enables a web based interface for vlc.</flag>
    <flag name="id3tag">Enables id3tag metadata reader plugin.</flag>
    <flag name="kate">Adds support for Ogg Kate subtitles via libkate.</flag>
    <flag name="libass">Enables subtitles support using libass.</flag>
    <flag name="libproxy">Enables support for proxy settings in the HTTP access module.</flag>
    <flag name="libsysfs">Get user key from firewire connected iPod via libsysfs.</flag>
    <flag name="libv4l">Enables Libv4l Video4Linux support.</flag>
    <flag name="libv4l2">Enables Libv4l2 Video4Linux2 support (for conversion
		from various video formats to standard ones, needed to use v4l2 devices
		with strange formats).</flag>
    <flag name="libtiger">Enables Ogg Kate subtitles rendering using libtiger.</flag>
    <flag name="live">Enables live555 streaming media support (client support for rtsp).</flag>
	<flag name="matroska">Enables matroska support using reference libraries (fallback on other existing matroska support if disabled, i.e., matroska enabled FFmpeg)</flag>
    <flag name="optimisememory">Enable optimisation for memory rather than performance.</flag>
    <flag name="pda">Builds a GTK+ interface suitable for PDA devices.</flag>
    <flag name="projectm">Enables the projectM visualization plugin.</flag>
    <flag name="pvr">Enables PVR cards access module.</flag>
    <flag name="qt4" restrict="&gt;=media-video/vlc-0.9">Builds a <pkg>x11-libs/qt</pkg> based frontend. It is now the most up-to-date graphical interface available.</flag>
    <flag name="remoteosd">Enables RemoteOSD plugin (VNC client as video filter).</flag>
    <flag name="rtsp">Enables real audio and RTSP modules.</flag>
    <flag name="run-as-root">Allows vlc to start for root. Don't enable this unless you have a very specific (e.g. embedded) need for it!</flag>
    <flag name="schroedinger">Enable Dirac video support (an advanced royalty-free video compression format) via libschroedinger (high-speed implementation in C of the Dirac codec).</flag>
    <flag name="sdl-image">Enables sdl image video decoder (depends on sdl)</flag>
    <flag name="shine">Enables shine fixed point mp3 encoder.</flag>
    <flag name="shout">Enables libshout output.</flag>
    <flag name="skins">Enables support for the skins2 interface.</flag>
    <flag name="stream">Enables vlc to stream video.</flag>
    <flag name="twolame">Enables twolame support (MPEG Audio Layer 2 encoder).</flag>
    <flag name="udev">Enables Linux udev services discovery.</flag>
    <flag name="upnp">Enables support for Intel UPnP stack.</flag>
	<flag name="vaapi">Enables VAAPI (Video Acceleration API) for hardware decoding</flag>
    <flag name="vcdinfo">Enables VCD information library support.</flag>
    <flag name="vcdx">Enables VCD with navigation via libvcdinfo (depends on cdio)</flag>
    <flag name="vlm">New videolan (media) manager (vlm), a little manager designed to launch and manage multiple streams from within one instance of VLC.</flag>
    <flag name="wma-fixed">Enables fixed point WMA decoder.</flag>
    <flag name="X">Enables support for, e.g., fullscreen mode via the X Window System. By itself, this flag does not build a graphical interface.</flag>
    <flag name="zvbi">Enables support for teletext subtitles via the zvbi library.</flag>
  </use>
</pkgmetadata>
